runmanclub.net 2016-03-15

# PRIVACY POLICY ~ Runmanclub

## Privacy Policy

At runmanclub.net, we collect some personal informations when you register on our site. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on runmanclub.net.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to runmanclub.net and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL  
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
Google Adsense  
Adbrite  
Advertising  
Adversal  
InfoLinks  
etc. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://runmanclub.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. 

runmanclub.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. runmanclub.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
